{
    "quizzes": [
        {
            "title": "week8",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "index": 1,
                    "question": "For a positive consumption externality,",
                    "options": ["SMB = PMB", "SMB = PMB − MD", "SMB = PMB + MB", "SMC = PMC / MD"],
                    "correct": "SMB = PMB + MB"
                },
                {
                    "index": 2,
                    "question": "For a positive production externality,",
                    "options": ["SMB = PMB", "SMB = PMB − MD", "SMB = PMB + MB", "SMC = PMC / MD"],
                    "correct": "SMB = PMB"
                },
                {
                    "index": 3,
                    "question": "The direct cost to producers of producing an additional unit of a good is",
                    "options": ["private marginal cost (PMC)", "social marginal cost (SMC)", "private marginal benefit (PMB)", "social marginal benefit (SMB)"],
                    "correct": "private marginal cost (PMC)"
                },
                {
                    "index": 4,
                    "question": "For a negative production externality,",
                    "options": ["SMC = PMC + MD", "SMC = PMC - MD", "SMC = PMC", "SMC = PMC - MB"],
                    "correct": "SMC = PMC + MD"
                },
                {
                    "index": 5,
                    "question": "The private marginal cost to producers plus any costs associated with the production of the good that are imposed on others is",
                    "options": ["private marginal cost (PMC)", "social marginal cost (SMC)", "private marginal benefit (PMB)", "social marginal benefit (SMB)"],
                    "correct": "social marginal cost (SMC)"
                },
                {
                    "index": 6,
                    "question": "Partying with loud noise is an example of",
                    "options": ["negative production externality", "positive production externality", "negative consumption externality", "positive consumption externality"],
                    "correct": "negative consumption externality"
                },
                {
                    "index": 7,
                    "question": "When an individual’s consumption increases the well-being of others, but the individual is not compensated by those others, we have",
                    "options": ["negative production externality", "positive production externality", "negative consumption externality", "positive consumption externality"],
                    "correct": "positive consumption externality"
                },
                {
                    "index": 8,
                    "question": "When a firm’s production increases the well-being of others but the firm is not compensated by those others, we have",
                    "options": ["negative production externality", "positive production externality", "negative consumption externality", "positive consumption externality"],
                    "correct": "positive production externality"
                },
                {
                    "index": 9,
                    "question": "When an individual’s consumption reduces the well-being of others who are not compensated by the individual, we have",
                    "options": ["negative production externality", "positive production externality", "negative consumption externality", "positive consumption externality"],
                    "correct": "negative consumption externality"
                },
                {
                    "index": 10,
                    "question": "For a negative consumption externality,",
                    "options": ["SMB = PMB", "SMB = PMB − MD", "SMB = PMB + MB", "SMC = PMC / MD"],
                    "correct": "SMB = PMB − MD"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}